NUR HASLIZA BINTI ZIZAN

No. 46, Jalan 61/10 Taman Koperasi Polis Fasa 2 Kuala Lumpur, W.P. K.L , 68100 013-257-0694 | lizazizan@ymail.com

OBJECTIVE

A challenging position in utilizing my interpersonal skills, technical skills with networking, operating systems, virtualization, Internet Information Server (IIS) and IT management system skills.

FUNCTIONAL SUMMARY

System Engineer with one year of experience in server and client based operating systems, virtualization for system internal testing, and Windows and Web-enabled application system. Efficient at networking, installing and configuring system application. Experienced in factory acceptance site (FAT), site acceptance test (SAT), preventive maintenance, installation and system configuration of servers, workstation and other endpoint devices. Dependable backup and restores of servers and workstation. Acquired other skills such as MSSQL, HTML, GIS, Microsoft Office and project management. Able to acquire new skills as required.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SEDIA TEGUH SDN. BHD, WANGSA MAJU, KUALA LUMPUR System Engineer, August 2016 – Present

- Responsible for providing system maintenance and configuration of Gas Management System (GMS) for Petronas Gas Berhad (PGB).
- Define and implement GMS as per in Functional Design Specification (FDS) to meet client requirements.
- Responsible of system installation, testing and evaluation.
- Performed system deployment at server workstations.
- Performed Preventive Maintenance as per scheduled.

LEMBAGA LEBUHRAYA MALAYSIA, KAJANG, SELANGOR Assistant IT Officer (Temporary Staff), May 2016 – August 2016

- Responsible of maintaining geospatial data into Geographic Information System (GIS) software.
- Responsible of providing geographical data into GIS system.
- Undertake observations data of XY coordinate for all highway construction in Malaysia.

WORLDTECH SOLUTIONS SDN. BHD, KOTA DAMANSARA, SELANGOR System Engineer (Intern), September 2015 – December 2015

- Performed on-site jobs in government and non-government sectors in 4 months as an intern.
- Handled ongoing Preventive Maintenance, Corrective Maintenance and Proof of Concept to end users.
- Handled software solution for Endpoint Management System (Desktop), Network Monitoring Software, IP Management System and Desktop virtualization solutions.

EDUCATION

- Bachelor of Computer Science in Data Communication & Networking, 3.05; UITM (2015)
- Diploma in Computer Science, 3.09; UITM (2012)
- PRA-London Chamber of Commerce & Industry (LCCI), IPB (2010)
- Sijil Peperiksaan Malaysia (SPM), Engineering Drawings(2009)

HOBBIES

· Sport, Gardening, Baking, Arts and Music.